<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Alejandro Beltran</title>
    <link>https://alejandrobeltran.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Alejandro Beltran</description>
    <image>
      <title>Alejandro Beltran</title>
      <url>https://alejandrobeltran.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://alejandrobeltran.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.133.1</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:56:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://alejandrobeltran.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Detecting Suspicious Companies</title>
      <link>https://alejandrobeltran.github.io/projects/list_of_projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Oct 2024 10:56:53 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alejandrobeltran.github.io/projects/list_of_projects/</guid>
      <description>By Alejandro Beltran
Project description Complicated company ownership structures are often set up to obfuscate the identification of beneficial owners. These strategies are considered to be on the fringe of legitimacy and legality, so detecting them is important to regulators and society in general. We combine economic theory, network analysis, and machine learning to unearth the patterns that such behaviours leave behind in large-scale administrative datasets. This allows us to identify clusters of companies that specialise in such strategies, and to formulate models about their potential adaptation to future legal reforms.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Local Authorities UK</title>
      <link>https://alejandrobeltran.github.io/projects/local_authorities/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://alejandrobeltran.github.io/projects/local_authorities/</guid>
      <description>By Alejandro Beltran
Project description Local governments provide a wide range of services within their areas. Financing these services is a constant issue as subnational governments across the world continue to accumulate responsibilities without a proportional ability to generate their own revenue. In order to better compare differences in taxing capacities and spending responsibilities between neighbouring local governments, this project presents various visualizations that facilitate that comparison. It relies on data from distinct sources to build a more complete picture of how local authorities in the UK mind the gap between spending and taxing.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
